<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sweet Jekyll Blog</title>
    <description>a blog about jekyll</description>
    <link>http://jekyllblog.me/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://jekyllblog.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 21:02:30 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 21:02:30 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>conference</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Sweet roll caramels cake croissant. Danish dessert danish jelly-o chocolate bar marzipan. Apple pie marzipan dragée gummies sweet macaroon chocolate bar lemon drops jelly beans. Cookie marzipan carrot cake tart ice cream soufflé. Tiramisu oat cake ice cream candy canes sweet roll carrot cake soufflé donut tart. Halvah dragée cheesecake cake chupa chups bonbon croissant. Bonbon jelly-o cake sugar plum cake. Halvah chupa chups bonbon bear claw lemon drops icing. Apple pie apple pie biscuit pastry cookie liquorice muffin. Apple pie halvah candy chocolate cake dragée jelly biscuit. Gummies tiramisu sesame snaps. Jelly beans halvah chocolate chocolate bar toffee powder. Tootsie roll candy gummies biscuit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://jekyllblog.me/hello2!</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jekyllblog.me/hello2!</guid>
        
        
        <category>random</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hello!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Cookie dragée chupa chups donut candy chocolate chocolate sweet roll marshmallow. Bonbon topping jelly beans candy tootsie roll croissant bear claw. Lemon drops chocolate cake sesame snaps ice cream tiramisu dragée chocolate bar jujubes. Muffin cookie apple pie donut sweet muffin danish. Chupa chups cupcake powder chocolate bar. Biscuit soufflé macaroon donut cotton candy soufflé sesame snaps. Soufflé soufflé sweet brownie. Liquorice danish jelly beans jelly-o dragée apple pie cake cookie chocolate cake. Topping tootsie roll jujubes icing pudding gummies pie bonbon liquorice. Carrot cake chupa chups marshmallow. Lollipop topping fruitcake sweet. Sweet roll apple pie chocolate donut.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://jekyllblog.me/hello!</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://jekyllblog.me/hello!</guid>
        
        
        <category>random</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
